现在女权主义者请来了律师
Now, the libbers are sending in attorneys,
我认为我们也应该找一个
and I think that we should have
英俊优秀的律师
a handsome, brilliant one on our side.
我不得不为此重新安排了一个重要会议
I had to reschedule a very important meeting because of this.
我明白  我很感激
I know. I'm so grateful you did.
你是我的杀手锏
You're my secret weapon.
立刻通过《平权修正案》
ERA now!
ERA now! ERA now!
女性不认为她们被婚姻所奴役
Our women do not consider themselves enslaved by marriage,
她们也不希望从家庭
and they do not wish to be liberated
和母亲身份中解放出来
from home and motherhood,
她们也绝对不想牺牲
and they certainly do not want to sacrifice
任何现有的特权
any of their present privileges
就为了达到和男性的虚假平等
for some phony equality with men.